[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "1 + 1 ?",
    "options": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "option": "1"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "option": "-1"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "option": "3"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "option": "2"
      }
    ],
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "3 + 2 x 5 ?",
    "options": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "option": "5"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "option": "10"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "option": "13"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "option": "9"
      }
    ],
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "2 x 2 x 0 - 1 ?",
    "options": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "option": "3"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "option": "-4"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "option": "0"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "option": "-1"
      }
    ],
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "11 x (5 - 4) ?",
    "options": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "option": "11"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "option": "22"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "option": "33"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "option": "0"
      }
    ],
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "10 / 2 - 3 x 2 ?",
    "options": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "option": "4"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "option": "-1"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "option": "-5"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "option": "-20"
      }
    ],
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "13 x 13 - 13 / 13 ?",
    "options": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "option": "1"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "option": "13.9"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "option": "169"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "option": "168"
      }
    ],
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "2² + 3² ?",
    "options": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "option": "25"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "option": "13"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "option": "16"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "option": "10"
      }
    ],
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "(2 + 3)² ?",
    "options": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "option": "25"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "option": "15"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "option": "10"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "option": "18"
      }
    ],
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "4² - 6 x 2 ?",
    "options": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "option": "-24"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "option": "24"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "option": "4"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "option": "2"
      }
    ],
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "((5)²)² ?",
    "options": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "option": "125"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "option": "625"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "option": "400"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "option": "720"
      }
    ],
    "answer": 2
  }
]